<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Glendon Hodges</title>
    <link>/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Glendon Hodges</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analytics reporting</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/calabrio-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/calabrio-analytics/</guid>
      <description>The functionality of the reports drove most of the demand for this software. I provided a brief explanation of report creation. The content structure was determined by the existing style of the Confluence space and Calabrio style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/cherwell-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/cherwell-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>As with most ML features, the difficult technology remains unseen by the user. A large part of my work involved using minimalist writing techniques to provide only what the user needed when they needed it. This involved brokering a compromise regarding what information is available to the different audiences involved in the project: end-user, customer administrator, and internal audiences (development, support, etc.).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message Queue Service</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/cherwell-mqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/cherwell-mqs/</guid>
      <description>A feature development team that I worked with at Cherwell replaced the message queue service with an open source option. After starting as a couple small topics to describe the implementation by development, the support team noticed repeated questions in customer calls. To reduce the number of support calls, I made iterative changes to the documentation to dig deeper into this application. The documentation set for this project evolved to encompass multiple configuration, and troubleshooting topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report creation</title>
      <link>/projects/creations/calabrio-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/creations/calabrio-reports/</guid>
      <description>This topic introduces the procedure for report creation in Calabrio Advanced Reporting. The information addresses an elementary step in using the reporting software. While providing this new information, it adheres to the existing style and topic structure for tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
